{
    "id": "a687b4d2829e4d43bf97780b81b0111f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The council ……………………………. of ten members.",
            "description": "Council is a singular subject, so write consists. ",
            "answers": [
                "consists",
                "consisting",
                "consist"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Later on he ………………………….. his mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "realized",
                "has realized",
                "was realized"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked ………………………… my name was.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. them for help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "asked to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the key I was ………………………….",
            "description": "To look for something is to search for it. ",
            "answers": [
                "looking",
                "searching",
                "seeing",
                "looking for"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. him to go.",
            "description": "We use tell before a personal object. ",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "spoke"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is used to ………………………….",
            "description": "Use an ing form after used to.",
            "answers": [
                "smoke",
                "smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………. the red shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "choose",
                "chose",
                "chosen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I would prefer to starve ………………………….. to beg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "rather",
                "rather than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. sitting there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "objected to my",
                "objected me",
                "objected with my"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to …………………………. for a while.",
            "description": "To lie down is to recline.",
            "answers": [
                "lie down",
                "lay down",
                "lain down"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If they informed me earlier, I ………………………… the function.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would/could/might + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "could attend",
                "can attend",
                "could have attended"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}